Guide to the Alfred E. Kahn papers, 1942-1994
Kahn, Alfred E. papers, 1942-1994
- Series XV. Articles
  - Southern California Gas Company, 1986 (Box 119, Folder 21)
  - Southwest Bell Oklahoma, 1985 (Box 119, Folder 22)
- Series XVI. Miscellaneous Documents
  - Test file, Eco. 501, 502, 352 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Economics 354 exam, 1969 (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Economics 353 exam, 1968 (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - Economics 351 exam (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - 351 Dispersed Industries (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Exams (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - 351 Miscellaneous Concentrations (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - 351 Miscellaneous Guideposts (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - 651 Total Monopoly problem (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - 651 Vertical integration (Box 131, Folder 10)
  - 651 Structure, Innovation, Growth (Box 131, Folder 11)
  - 651 Concentration (Box 131, Folder 12)
  - Palestine (Box 131, Folder 13)
  - Frank Graham, Dollar Shortage Articles (Box 131, Folder 14)
  - Italy--US Antitrust (Box 131, Folder 15)
  - Proposed Text- International Monetary Economics (Box 131, Folder 16)
  - Frank Graham (Box 131, Folder 17)
  - Exchange Rate Changes (Box 131, Folder 18)
  - Tenion Producing (Box 131, Folder 19)
  - 61-1 Foster Rebuttal (Box 131, Folder 20)
  - 61-1 (Box 131, Folder 21)
  - 61-1 Wenner, 1964 (Box 131, Folder 22)
  - Rate Design, 1963 (Box 131, Folder 23)
  - Replacement Cost approaches (Box 131, Folder 24)
  - RAR, 1961 (Box 131, Folder 25)
  - Pipeline economics and storage, 1961 (Box 131, Folder 26)
  - National Gas Survey, 1973 (Box 131, Folder 27)
  - McAvoy, 1961 (Box 131, Folder 28)
  - Gas- 64-1, 1965 (Box 131, Folder 29)
  - Gas regulation, 1969-1973 (Box 131, Folder 30)
  - End Use control (Box 131, Folder 31)
  - Price Discrimination (Box 131, Folder 32)
  - Cost Trends, 1962 (Box 131, Folder 33)
  - Cost Allocation methods, 1957 (Box 131, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 131, Folder 35)
  - Certification, 1956 (Box 131, Folder 36)
  - Argument Testimony Brief (Box 131, Folder 37)
  - Project (Box 131, Folder 38)
  - Statements (Box 131, Folder 39)
  - US Federal Power Commission (Box 131, Folder 40)
  - US Federal Power Commission (Box 131, Folder 41)
  - Public Service of Indiana (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Shoreham/LILCO (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Shoreham/LILCO (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Shoreham commission (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - Shoreham commission (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - AT+T (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - The Depletion Allowance in the context of Cartelization, 1964 (Box 132, Folder 9)
  - Sawhill Commission (Box 132, Folder 10)
  - Sawhill Commission (Box 132, Folder 11)
  - Skybus (Box 132, Folder 12)
  - FIAT Money Inflatin in France, AD White (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Econ 651 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Drafts of early articles (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous documents, 1968-1974 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous documents, 1968-1975 (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous documents, 1968-1976 (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous documents, 1953-1958 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - AG Committee Correspondence (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - Taxes, 1974 (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - Oil Book (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - Oil-Correspondence (Box 133, Folder 11)
  - Interviews- AEK (Box 133, Folder 12)
  - Integration (Box 133, Folder 13)
  - Honolulu Oil (Box 133, Folder 14)
  - Galbraith, John Kenneth (Box 133, Folder 15)
  - McGee Bork (Box 133, Folder 16)
  - Liberalism, 1960 (Box 133, Folder 17)
  - Legislation Pending (Box 133, Folder 18)
  - ADH Kaplan (Box 133, Folder 19)
  - Ithaca Theaters, 1967-1968 (Box 133, Folder 20)
  - Monopoly and Stagnation Italy (Box 133, Folder 21)
  - NY Stock Exchange (Box 133, Folder 22)
  - Oil Misc., 1952 (Box 133, Folder 23)
  - Patents (Box 133, Folder 24)
  - Price Commission, 1972 (Box 133, Folder 25)
  - Concentration (Box 133, Folder 26)
  - Antitrust Committee (Box 133, Folder 27)
  - Dewey (Box 133, Folder 28)
  - Notebook, 1940s (Box 133, Folder 29)
  - NBR Commentaries, 1984-1985 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Nightly Business Report Commentaries, 1989-1993 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - Nightly Business Report Commentaries, 1986-1987 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - Nightly Business Report Commentaries, 1988-1989 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Notebooks (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Electric and Utility regulation (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - Letters from and to airline pilots (Box 134, Folder 8)
  - Econ 353 (Box 134, Folder 9)
  - Boces Talk (Box 134, Folder 10)
  - AEK Class notes (Box 134, Folder 11)
  - Econ 201, 1989 (Box 134, Folder 12)
  - Cornell articles (Box 134, Folder 13)
  - Ithaca miscellaneous (Box 134, Folder 14)
  - Editorials clippings AEK (Box 134, Folder 15)
  - Thompson Medicinal company (Box 134, Folder 16)
  - Tie Communications (Box 134, Folder 17)
  - Western Union (Box 134, Folder 18)
  - White House File (Box 134, Folder 19)
  - White House Personal (Box 134, Folder 20)
  - Whyte, William (Box 134, Folder 21)
  - Wind Farms (Box 134, Folder 22)
  - Wirth Bill (Box 134, Folder 23)
  - "The Folklore of Capitalism" (Box 134, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous notes (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Public Service Commission cases (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Publications (Box 135, Folder 7)
- Series XVII. Initial Collection Acquisition
  - U.S. Federal Power Commission Area Rate Proceeding - Permian Basin Area (AR61-1), ca. 1961-1968 (Box 1)
  - U.S. Federal Power Commission Area Rate Proceeding - Southern Louisiana Area (AR62-2), ca. 1961-1970 (Box 2)
  - U.S. Federal Power Commission - Tidewater Oil Company (G-13310 et al.), 1955-1961 (Box 3)
  - U.S. Federal Power Commission Champlin Oil and Refining Company, et al. (G-9277 et al.), 1959 (Box 3)
  - U.S. Federal Power Commission - Continental Oil Company, et al. (G-11024, et al.), 1961 (Box 4)
  - U.S. Federal Power Commission - Phillips Petroleum Company (G-1148, et al.), ca. 1956-1960 (Box 4)
  - U.S. Federal Power Commission - Gulf Oil Corporation, et al. (G-9520, et al.), 1959-1961 (Box 4)
  - U.S. Federal Power Commission - Sohio Petroleum Company, et al. (G-8488, et al.), ca. 1958 (Box 4)
  - Proved Discoveries and Productive Capacities of Crude Oil, Natural Gas, and Natural Gas Liquids in the United States, National Petroleum Council, 1961 (Box 4)
  - Interim Report: The Pricing of New Contract Gas Within the Framework of a Two-Price System, n.d. (Box 4)
  - U.S. v. Standard Oil Company, Pan American Petroleum Corporation, and Tidewater Oil Company, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 1-3)
  - Honolulu anti-trust case, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 4-5)
  - Honolulu anti-trust case - first draft of testimony, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Honolulu anti-trust case - footnotes, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Small box of notes for The Position of Great Britain in the World Economy, Kahn's Ph.D. dissertation, ca. 1942 (Box 6)
  - Two annotated typescripts (one bound) of The Position of Great Britain in the World Economy, 1942 (Box 6)
  - Drafts and typescripts of The Economics of Regulation, Chapters 8-10, ca. 1970 (Box 6)
  - Drafts and typescripts of The Economics of Regulation, Chapters 11-14 and 27; references; and index, ca. 1970 (Box 7)
  - Last draft of The Economics of Regulation, Vol. II, pp. i-287, ca. 1970 (Box 7)
  - Last draft of The Economics of Regulation, Vol. II, pp. 288-938 and index, ca. 1970 (Box 8)
  - Academic freedom (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Afro-American Society (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Arts College (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Brown Committee (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Center for International Studies (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Commission on Undergraduate Education (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Instruction - background (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Instruction - clippings (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Instruction - current (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Instruction - memos (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Instruction - faculty response (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Instruction - minutes, notes (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Cornell Aeronautical Lab (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Cottrell-Rossiter (Liberal Education Committee) (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Instruction - studies (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Curriculum (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Economics department (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Council (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Council (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Council (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Faculty Council (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Fraternities (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Kreast Reports (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Medical plans (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - ROTC (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Speech & Drama (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Students (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Board of Trustees (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - University staff (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Antitrust Bulletin (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Talks - Alumni groups (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Kennedy - Keating (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Speeches - Current macro conditions (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Speeches - Capitalism, etc. (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Econ 351 Syllabi (Box 9, Folder 35-36)
  - Econ 353 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Econ 104 TA instructions (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - 651 handouts (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - 104 Problems and handouts (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - 104 Exams (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - "Mountain Talk" (1972) by Archie Ammons for Kahn, 2 cartoons and a certificate, Folder in Manuscript Box (Box 85)
- Series XVIII. Videos
  - The Regulatory Session; Workshop on Local Access: Strategies for Public Policy, TR-6227 (Box 137)
    In brown briefcase; rubber-bound with TR-6228.
  - The Future of Access; Workshop on Local Access: Strategies for Public Policy, TR-6228 (Box 137)
    In brown briefcase; rubber-bound with TR-6227.
  - BBC Interview; Washington, D.C., c. Jan. 1979; TR-6229 (Box 137)
    In brown briefcase.
  - Middlebury Talk; Relevance of Industrial Organization, Part I, Apr. 17, 1981; TR-6230 (Box 137)
  - Middlebury Talk; Relevance of Industrial Organization, Part II, Apr. 17, 1981; TR-6231 (Box 137)
  - Reg. Anti-Infla. Seminar; New York, N.Y., Mar. 28, 1979; TR-6232 (Box 137)
  - Am. Ins. Assoc.; Washington, D.C., Mar. 23, 1979; TR-6233 (Box 137)
  - CPI Press Conf.; Washington, D.C., Mar. 23, 1979; TR-6234 (Box 137)
  - Detroit Economic Club; Detroit, Mich., Feb. 26, 1979; TR-6235 (Box 137)
  - Nat'l Newspaper Assoc. Anti-Infla. Conf.; Washington, D.C., Mar. 16, 1979; TR-6236 (Box 137)
  - Barbara Walters (ABC) Interview; Washington, D.C., c. Feb. 1979; TR-6237 (Box 137)
  - Cornell WHCU Dimension Series; Ithaca, N.Y., Nov. 9-10, 1978; TR-6238 (Box 137)
  - Fla. Council of 100; Tampa, Florida, Feb. 1, 1979; TR-6239 (Box 137)
  - NARUC Tech. Educ. Conf. for Commi.; Washington, D.C., Feb. 20, 1979; TR-6240 (Box 137)
  - Irving R. Levine (NBC) Interview; Washington, D.C., c. May 1979; TR-6241 (Box 137)
  - Univ. of Mass. Commencement; Amherst, Mass., May 26, 1979; TR-6242 (Box 137)
  - CPI Press Conf.; Washington, D.C., May 25, 1979; TR-6243 (Box 137)
  - Investment CO. Inst.; San Francisco, CA (Speech), May 17, 1979; TR-6244 (Box 137)
  - Investment CO. Inst.; San Francisco, CA (Speech), May 16, 1979/80 (?); TR-6245 (Box 137)
    In brown briefcase; "5-16-80" typed on label but "5/16/79" hand-written on tape.
  - Demo. Nat'l Finance Council Lunch Speech; Washington, D.C. (Sides 1 and 2), May 8, 1979; TR-6246 (Box 137)
  - Demo. Nat'l Finance Council Lunch Speech; Washington, D.C. (Side 3), May 8, 1979; TR-6247 (Box 137)
  - Wall Street Week Interview; New York, N.Y., Dec. 1, 1978; TR-6248 (Box 137)
  - Sherry Henry (WOR) Interview; Washington, D.C., Jul. 10, 1980; TR-6249 (Box 137)
  - CPI with reporters; Washington, D.C., May 23, 1980; TR-6250 (Box 137)
  - National Urban Coalition Speech, Jan. 10, 1979; TR-6251 (Box 137)
  - Henry H. Fowler Visiting Scholar Talk: "Regulation - Deregulation"; Olin Hall Theater (8 PM), Jan. 10, 1983; TR-6252 (Box 137)
  - Problems of Governance in an Inflation-Prone Society, Jul. 12, 1981; TR-6253 (Box 137)
  - Chemical Manufacturers Assoc., TR-6254 (Box 137)
  - 1981 Outlook: "Another Dip or a Real Recession?" by Dr. A. Gary Shilling, Jan. 9, 1981; TR-6255 (Box 137)
  - Al Carlson Interview, Oct. 10, 1980; TR-6256 (Box 137)
  - Dr. Kahn's Speech, Apr. 28, 1982; TR-6257 (Box 137)
  - Henry H. Fowler Lecture Series (2:30 PM), Jan. 10, 1983; TR-6258 (Box 137)
  - Senate Banking Comm. Testimony; Washington, D.C. (Sides 3 and 4), Mar. 17, 1980; TR-6259 (Box 137)
  - "Level Playing Fields" Q and A with Alfred Kahn, TR-6260 (Box 137)
  - Barbara Mink's Interview with AEK, Feb. 18, 1981; TR-6261 (Box 137)
  - Joint Economic Comm. Testimony; Washington, D.C. (Sides 1 and 2), Aug. 22, 1980; TR-6262 (Box 137)
  - AEK's Talk at Washington Office, May 9, 1984; TR-6263 (Box 137)
  - Susan Waters Fairchild Publications, Aug. 1, 1980; TR-6264 (Box 137)
  - Nina Sutton (Paris Match) Interview, Jul. 30, 1980; TR-6265 (Box 137)
  - Ames: Uneasy Marriage Q and A, May 16, 1984; TR-6266 (Box 137)
  - Henry H. Fowler Lecture Series (10 AM), Jan. 11, 1983; TR-6267 (Box 137)
    Includes a hand-written Post-It note: "Roanoke College / Salem VA / January 9-10, 1983".
  - Rato Interesso, TR-6268 (Box 137)
  - Interview with Dick Bartel for Challenge Magazine Article, Sep. 3, 1981; TR-6269 (Box 137)
    Bound with tape to TR-6270.
  - Interview with Dick Bartel for Challenge Magazine Article, Sep. 3, 1981; TR-6270 (Box 137)
    Bound with tape to TR-6269.
  - Meet the Press Interview; Washington, D.C., Oct. 29, 1978; TR-6271 (Box 137)
  - Tolls Lecture at SUNY Genesco: "Responsible Public Behavior and the Control of Inflation", Apr. 13, 1981; TR-6272 (Box 137)
  - Senate Banking Comm. Testimony; Washington, D.C. (Sides 1 and 2), Mar. 17, 1980; TR-6273 (Box 137)
  - Chamber of Comm. Breakfast; Calhounco, AL, Sep. 4, 1980; TR-6274 (Box 137)
  - Joint Economic Comm. CPI Testimony; Washington, D.C., Jun. 24, 1980; TR-6275 (Box 137)
  - Joint Economic Comm. Testimony; Washington, D.C., Jan. 25, 1980; TR-6276 (Box 137)
  - Consumer Federation of America Speech; Washington, D.C., Feb. 8, 1979; TR-6277 (Box 137)
  - W.H. Conf. on SM. Business Speech; Atlanta, GA, Feb. 15, 1979; TR-6278 (Box 137)
  - Face the Nation Interview; Washington, D.C., Mar. 4, 1979; TR-6279 (Box 137)
  - Chicago Economic Club Speech; Chicago, IL, Mar. 13, 1979; TR-6280 (Box 137)
  - Nat'l Assoc. of Manufactureres Speech; Washington, D.C., Mar. 29, 1979; TR-6281 (Box 137)
  - Meeting with Health Experts; Washington D.C. (Sides 1 and 2), Dec. 11, 1979; TR-6282 (Box 137)
  - Joint Economic Comm. Testimony; Washington, D.C. (Side 3), Aug. 22, 1980; TR-6283 (Box 137)
  - Common Cause 10th Anniversary; Washington, D.C., Sep. 5, 1980; TR-6284 (Box 137)
  - Ed Cowan (N.Y. Times) Interview; Washington, D.C., Sep. 8, 1980; TR-6285 (Box 137)
  - Women in Government Relations Speech; Four Seasons Hotel, Washington, D.C., Sep. 12, 1980; TR-6286 (Box 137)
  - Reg. Ref. Conf. Q and A; Raliegh, N.C., Sep. 30, 1980; TR-6287 (Box 137)
  - Ralph Blumenthal (N.Y. Times) Interview; Washington, D.C. (Sides 3 and 4), Oct. 20, 1980; TR-6288 (Box 137)
  - Ralph Blumenthal (N.Y. Times) Interview; Washington, D.C. (Sides 1 and 2), Oct. 20, 1980; TR-6289 (Box 137)
  - Emily Soapes (Presidential Papers Staff) Interview, Oct. 21, 1980; TR-6290 (Box 137)
  - Robert Greenberger (Wall Street Journal) Interview, Oct. 22, 1980; TR-6291 (Box 137)
  - Sim Fentress (Time Magazine) Interview, Oct. 24, 1980; TR-6292 (Box 137)
  - Theodore White (The Making of the Pres.) Interview, Oct. 27, 1980; TR-6293 (Box 137)
  - Don May (UPI) Interview; Washington, D.C., Nov. 4, 1980; TR-6294 (Box 137)
  - Glenn Ritt (AP) Interview; Washington, D.C., Nov. 4, 1980; TR-6295 (Box 137)
  - Meryl Gordon (Gannett News Service) Interview; Washington, D.C., Nov. 4, 1980; TR-6296 (Box 137)
  - Bill Blaylock (Time Magazine) Interview; Washington, D.C., Nov. 6, 1980; TR-6297 (Box 137)
  - John Walcott (Newsweek) Interview; Washington, D.C., Jun. 26, 1980; TR-6298 (Box 137)
  - Moorhead Subcomm. Testimony; Washington, D.C., Mar. 19, 1980; TR-6299 (Box 137)
  - Cattle/Caffle (?), Mar. 18, 1980; TR-6300 (Box 137)
    The title is hand-written on the label and (is more likely the first but) could be either one.
  - Senate Finance Comm. Testimony (Side 1) / Health Subcomm. Testimony (Side 2), Mar. 19, 1980; TR-6301 (Box 137)
  - Senior Citizens of New York Speech, Mar. 20, 1980; TR-6302 (Box 137)
  - House Approp. Subc. on Treas. Testimony; Washington, D.C., Mar. 30, 1980; TR-6303 (Box 137)
  - Senate Banking Comm. Testimony; Washington, D.C. (Sides 3 and 4), Apr. 21, 1980; TR-6304 (Box 137)
  - Senate Banking Comm. Testimony; Washington, D.C. (Sides 1 and 2), Apr. 21, 1980; TR-6305 (Box 137)
  - Senate Approp. Comm. Testimony; Washington, D.C. (Sides 3 and 4), Apr. 23, 1980; TR-6306 (Box 137)
  - Senate Approp. Comm. Testimony; Washington, D.C. (Sides 1 and 2), Apr. 23, 1980; TR-6307 (Box 137)
  - House Banking Economic Stabilization Testimony; Washington, D.C. (Sides 1 and 2), May 6, 1980; TR-6308 (Box 137)
  - House Banking Economic Stabilization Testimony; Washington, D.C. (Sides 3 and 4), May 6, 1980; TR-6309 (Box 137)
  - George Straight (ABC News) Interview; Washington, D.C., May 9, 1980; TR-6310 (Box 137)
  - Chemical Manufacturers Assoc. Speech, May 13, 1980; TR-6311 (Box 137)
  - Ripon College Commencement Address; Ripon, WI, May 18, 1980; TR-6312 (Box 137)
  - Press Conference at Ripon College; Ripon, WI, May 18, 1980; TR-6313 (Box 137)
  - Joint Economic Comm. Testimony; Washington, D.C., May 23, 1980; TR-6314 (Box 137)
  - Jeff Hodes (KRON-TV) Interview; San Francisco, CA, May 23, 1980; TR-6315 (Box 137)
  - Group W Radio Interview, May 29, 1980; TR-6316 (Box 137)
  - Hildreth (Newhouse Newspapers) Interview; Washington, D.C., May 30, 1980; TR-6317 (Box 137)
  - Binghamton, N.Y. Speech, Jun. 19, 1980; TR-6318 (Box 137)
  - D. Vietor (ALD 210), Mar. 21, 1985; TR-6319 (Box 137)
  - Reunion Speech to Cornell Alumni in Bailey Hall; Ithaca, N.Y., Jun. 8, 1979; TR-10465 (Box 138)
  - KTAR News Radio Interview; Phoenix, AZ, c. 1980; TR-10466 (Box 138)
  - COWPS Press Conference; Washington, D.C., Apr. 3, 1980; TR-10467 (Box 138)
  - COWPS Welcome Briefing; Washington, D.C., Apr. 15, 1980; TR-10468 (Box 138)
  - Jun. 11, 1979, TR-10469 (Box 138)
    The title label is missing and the title is unlisted on the "Tape Information Sheet".
  - Press Conference; Washington, D.C., Aug. 7, 1979; TR-10470 (Box 138)
  - All Things Considered (NPR) Interview; Washington, D.C., TR-10471 (Box 138)
  - Boston Tape 9, V-7102 (Box 138)
    The front label has the date "4-12-79" but the inside of the case and the tape itself have the date "3-28-79".
  - "Economically Speaking: A Conversation with Alfred Kahn" (WQLN Channel 54), V-7103 (Box 138)
  - Firing Line with Alfred Kahn (Prices and Pricing), V-7104 (Box 138)
  - Jim Jensen Interview; New York, N.Y., Jul. 10, 1980; V-7105 (Box 138)
  - Time to Talk with Alfred Kahn, V-7106 (Box 138)
  - Town Meeting/Inflation, Dec. 20, 1978; V-7107 (Box 138)
  - "NBR etc. full", V-7108 (Box 139)
    The spine label is a mess of scribbles with the provided title as the most visible.
  - Special Production / Continental / World Wide Performance / Celebration, V-7109 (Box 139)
    Also, the label on the spine has a hand-written note: "Me at 448-90".
  - "Me on MacNeil / Lehrer", V-7110 (Box 139)
  - Regulation in Transition (Tape 6), May 8, 1995; V-7111 (Box 139)
    Hand-written label on the spine reads: "FRED TALK on Electric dereg".
  - CPUC: Universal Telephone Service Full Panel Hearing (Tape 1), Sep. 29, 1995; V-7112 (Box 139)
  - NBR / Mag[nificent] Ambersons, V-7113 (Box 139)
    The label on the VHS tape reads: "All the Vermeers in NY / Mystery #1".
  - AEK and NBR: Early '80s and 1990, V-7114 (Box 139)
    Chinatown is still faintly visible on the VHS label.
  - Iran-Contra: The Story Behind the Scandal, c. 1986; V-7115 (Box 139)
  - Economics U$A: "Oligopolies", V-7116 (Box 139)
    Hand-written on the case spine: "(incl. AEK on airline reg + dereg)".
  - Nightline - AEK, Sep. 27, 1983; V-7117 (Box 139)
  - CBS Nightwatch, Jan. 5, 1983; V-7118 (Box 139)
  - The KMB Video Journal: "The Wireless World and Its Relationship to the Wireline Infrastructure, Pt. I" (V. 9, No. 2), V-7119 (Box 139)
  - The KMB Video Journal: "A National Perspective on Telecommunications Pricing" (V. 1, No. 2), V-7120 (Box 139)
  - Dr. Alfred Kahn Speech to LPPC, V-7121 (Box 139)
  - Alfred Kahn at MIT, Jun. 16, 1981; V-7122 (Box 139)
  - North Carolina Alternative Energy Corporation (NCAEC) Least-Cost Energy Planning for the Carolinas (Conference Highlights), c. Oct. 1988; V-7123 (Box 139)
  - GA Airline Dereg., Jul. 21, 1988; V-7124 (Box 139)
  - NBR, Feb. 14, 1986; V-7125 (Box 139)
    The spine label is a mess of scribbles with the provided title as the most logical summary of the VHS's contents; the most visible titles are actually "Fred Astaire Sings" and "Kents: Max + Helen".
  - Cornell University Johnson Graduate School of Management: Leadership for the Twenty-First Century; People and Programs: A Celebration of the Capital Campaign Achievements, c. Oct. 1989; V-7126 (Box 139)
  - Fred NBR / Nightline with MacNeil and Lehrer, V-7127 (Box 139)
    Taped over, as the crossed-out label indicates, To Have and To [sic] Have Not.
  - "Fred NBR's etc.", V-7128 (Box 139)
    Taped over the TV mini-series The Charterhouse of Parma and "Ballet".
  - Continental Airlines: Kahn Modules, Sep. 16, 1987; V-7129 (Box 139)
  - California Institute of Technology/MIT Presentation of R.D. Neumann/Calif. Air Shuttle; Enterprise Forum, Jun. 23, 1990; V-7130 (Box 139)
  - The World's Economy, Parts I and II; Fingerlakes Forum, c. Dec. 1990; V-7131 (Box 139)
  - Ketchum New York: New York Air - Alfred Kahn Rough Cuts, Nov. 10, 1981; V-7132 (Box 139)
    Brief summary of VHS contents on VHS label.
  - NBR (Nov. 13, 24, 27 and Dec. 4, 1981), Various Dates (see title); V-7133 (Box 139)
  - Profiles from Home, V-7134 (Box 139)
    A Post-It note is attached to the case; it is a thank you letter to Alfred Kahn from Regina Deschere of Time Warner.
  - Harvard Business School: Alfred Kahn - Civil Aeronautics Board, Mar. 27, 1985; V-7135 (Box 139)
    "Part I: Marginalism in New York; Part II: Edited Remarks".
  - NBR and MacNeil and Lehrer, Jan. 29, 1987; V-7136 (Box 139)
    Other titles on the spine of the case include: "Random Harvest / Dancer / MP #2".
  - Alfred Kahn Commentary, Oct. 21, 1988; V-7137 (Box 139)
    Taped over the TV mini-series Smiley [sic] People (3-6).
  - Economics U$A Program #20: "Oligopolies", V-7138 (Box 139)
  - AEK - Dereg. / Airlines - Adam Smith, Jun. 9, 1985; V-7139 (Box 139)
    A Post-It note is attached to the case; it reads, in hand-writing, "To: AEK / From: JHG".
  - AEK - NBR, Aug. 16, 1982; V-7140 (Box 139)
    A Post-It note is attached to the case; it reads, in hand-writing, "To: AEK / From: JHG / Nightly Bus. Report / 8-16-82".
  - "NBR + 2/8 Good A.M.", V-7141 (Box 139)
    The date, Feb. 8th, is provided but the year is not.
  - The NBR for March 28, 1986, Apr. 17, 1986; V-7142 (Box 139)
  - AEK - NBR / Nightwatch / Feynman, Jul. 9, 1982; V-7143 (Box 139)
  - Face the Nation Interview (Oct. 14, 1979); WRC-TV Local New Center Interview (Oct. 30, 1979); Good Morning America Interviews (Jan. 1, 1980 and Apr. 3, 1980), Various Dates (see title); V-7144 (Box 140)
  - Helen Whalen (WPBT Miami) Interview; Washington, D.C., Sep. 9, 1980; V-7145 (Box 140)
  - AM Pittsburgh Interview, Oct. 31, 1980; V-7146 (Box 140)
    Inside the case is a signed thank you letter from the AM Pittsburgh producer.
  - Public Policy Forum Speech; Washington, D.C., Jan. 7, 1979; V-7147 (Box 140)
  - MacNeil/Lehrer Report Interview; Washington, D.C., Aug. 28, 1980; V-7148 (Box 140)
  - Inflation Briefing and Q and A with Mr. Wurfel; Washington, D.C. (Tape IV), V-7149 (Box 140)